http://www.oceanfirstdivers.com/privacy-policy

OCEAN FIRST DIVER’S WEBSITE PRIVACY STATEMENT
Effective Date:  This Terms of Use Agreement was last updated on April 15th, 2007
1. Scope
This Privacy Policy describes how we handle your personal information for our services on the Ocean First Divers website. It applies generally to the Oceanfirstdivers.com website and other related websites where this policy appears in the footer of the page (“the Sites”). Some websites we operate may be governed by separate privacy policies. The policy that applies on any of our domains or subdomains is always the policy that appears in the footer of each website.
By accepting the Privacy Policy and the User Agreement in registration, you expressly consent to our collection, storage, use and disclosure of your personal information as described in this Privacy Policy. This Privacy Policy is effective upon acceptance for new users and is otherwise effective on April 15th, 2007.
2. Collection
You can browse the Sites without telling us who you are or revealing any personal information about yourself. Once you give us your personal information, you are not anonymous to us. If you choose to provide us with personal information, you consent to the transfer and storage of that information to our servers located in the United States.
We may collect and store the following personal information:
email address, physical contact information, and (depending on the service used) sometimes financial information, such as credit card or bank account numbers;
transactional information based on your activities on the Sites (such as buying, selling, item and content you generate or that relates to your account);
shipping, billing and other information you provide to purchase or ship an item;
correspondence through the Site, and correspondence sent to us;
computer sign-on data, statistics on page views, traffic to and from the Site, and ad data;
other information, including IP address and standard web log information.
3. Marketing
We don't sell or rent your personal information to third parties for their marketing purposes without your explicit consent. We may combine your information with information we collect from other companies (such as demographic data) to improve and personalize our services. If you don't wish to receive marketing communications from us, simply indicate your preference once you sign-in or by following the directions within the email.
4. Acknowledgement and acceptance of terms
Ocean First Divers, LLC is committed to protecting your privacy. This Privacy Statement sets forth our current privacy practices with regard to the information we collect when you or your computer interact with our website.   By accessing www.oceanfirstdivers.com, you acknowledge and fully understand Ocean First Divers, LLC’s Privacy Statement and freely consent to the information collection and use practices described in this Website Privacy Statement.
5. Participating Merchant Policies
Related services and offerings with links from this website, including vendor sites, have their own privacy statements that can be viewed by clicking on the corresponding links within each respective website. Online merchants and others who participate in Ocean First Divers, LLC services are encouraged to participate in industry privacy initiatives and to take a responsible attitude towards consumer privacy.  However, since we do not have direct control over the policies or practices of participating merchants and other third parties, we are not responsible for the privacy practices or contents of those sites.  We recommend and encourage that you always review the privacy policies of merchants and other third parties before you provide any personal information or complete any transaction with such parties.
6. Our Disclosure of Your Information
We may disclose personal information to respond to legal requirements, enforce our policies, respond to claims, or protect anyone's rights, property, or safety.
We may also share your personal information with:
members of our corporate family to help detect and prevent potentially illegal acts and provide joint services; (Our corporate affiliates will market only to users who request these services.)
service providers under contract who help with our business operations.
other third parties to whom you explicitly ask us to send your information; (or about whom you are otherwise explicitly notified and consent to when using a specific service)
law enforcement or other governmental officials, in response to a verified request relating to a criminal investigation or alleged illegal activity.
other business entities, should we plan to merge with or be acquired by that business entity. (Should such a combination occur, we would require that the new combined entity follow this privacy policy with respect to your personal information. If your personal information will be used contrary to this policy, you will receive prior notice.)
Without limiting the above, in an effort to respect your privacy and our ability to keep the community free from bad actors, we will not otherwise disclose your personal information to law enforcement, other government officials, or other third parties without a subpoena, court order or substantially similar legal procedure, except when we believe in good faith that the disclosure of information is necessary to prevent imminent physical harm or financial loss or to report suspected illegal activity.
7. Security
Your information is stored on our servers located in the United States. We treat data as an asset that must be protected. However, third parties may unlawfully intercept or access transmissions or private communications, and other users may abuse or misuse your personal information that they collect from the Site. Therefore, although we work very hard to protect your privacy, we do not promise, and you should not expect, that your personal information or private communications would always remain private.
8. Use of Web Beacons or GIF files
Ocean First Divers, LLC web pages may contain electronic images known as Web beacons – sometimes also called single-pixel gifs – that allow Ocean First Divers, LLC to count users who have visited those pages and to deliver co-branded services.  Ocean First Divers, LLC may include Web beacons in promotional e-mail messages or newsletters in order to determine whether messages have been opened and acted upon.
Some of these Web beacons may be placed by third party service providers to help determine the effectiveness of our advertising campaigns or email communications.  These Web beacons may be used by these service providers to place a persistent cookie on your computer.  This allows the service provider to recognize your computer each time you visit certain pages or emails and compile anonymous information in relation to those page views, which in turn enables us and our service providers to learn which advertisements and emails bring you to our website and how you use the site.  Ocean First Divers, LLC prohibits Web beacons from being used to collect or access your personal information.
9. Accessing Web Account Information
We will provide you with the means to ensure that personally identifiable information in your web account file is correct and current.  You may review this information by contacting us by sending an email to our support attendant, INFO@OCEANFIRSTDIVERS.COM.
10. Third Parties
Except as otherwise expressly included in this Privacy Policy, this document addresses only the use and disclosure of information we collect from you. If you disclose your information to others, different rules may apply to their use or disclosure of the information you disclose to them. Since Ocean First Divers does not control the privacy policies of third parties, you are subject to the privacy policies of those third parties. We encourage you to ask questions before you disclose your personal information to others.
11. Changes to this Statement
Ocean First Divers, LLC has the discretion to occasionally update this privacy statement.  When we do, we will also revise the “updated” date at the top of this Privacy page.  We encourage you to periodically review this privacy statement to stay informed about how we are helping to protect the personal information we collect.  Your continued use of the service constitutes your agreement to this privacy statement and any updates.
12. Contacting Us
If you have questions regarding our Privacy Statement, its implementation, failure to adhere to this Privacy Statement and/or our general practices, please contact us at INFO@OCEANFIRSTDIVERS.COM or send your comments to:
Ocean First Divers, LLC
Attention:  Privacy Statement Personal
3015 Bluff St.
Boulder, CO 80301
Ocean First Divers, LLC will use commercially reasonable efforts to promptly respond and resolve any problem or question.
HOURS:
MON-FRI 10AM-7PM // SAT 10AM-6PM // SUN 12PM-5PM
